http://www.bouchardfinlayson.co.za/about/legal/cookie-policy

By using this site you are accepting our use of cookies to help provide the best possible service and experience.
Please refer to our Privacy and Cookie Policy to read more about the cookies we use and how to change your settings.
Site Search
Telephone:
You are here:
Home
About Us
Legal
Cookie Policy
Red Carnation Hotels UK Ltd.
Cookie Policy
Last updated: 10th June 2019
Please click on a link below to jump to a specific paragraph:
5. Changes to our cookie policy
6. How to disable cookies?
7. Rejecting cookies
8. Further information
9. Contacting us
1. About the policy
This Cookie Policy (“Policy”) describes Red Carnation Hotels UK Ltd ’s collection, use, and retention of the cookies present on the website.
Cookies are simple text files that help coordinateRed Carnation Hotels UK Ltd ’s website servers and your browser to display the full range of features offered by us. These features include hassle-free automatic logins and authentication, shopping cart functionality, third party ad serving, ad management, preference setting, and language setting, among others.
We require your consent to process cookies, unless you provide us with your personal information, for instance for registration, placing an order, or complete online forms. In this case, we may collect, store and use your personal information in accordance to our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read this document.
2. About us
This is the privacy policy of Red Carnation Hotels UK Ltd. (referred to as "we", "us" or "our").
We are incorporated under the laws of England and Wales. Our incorporation number is 3328595 and our incorporation address or registered office is 35 Charles Street, London, W1J 5EBV. [We are a member of ABTA (Y181X) and licensed by the Civil Aviation Authority (10148).]
3. Cookie Law
Also known as the 'Cookie Directive', the instrument that defines the requirements for consent for cookies across the EU is Directive 2009/136/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council, an excerpt of which is reproduced below:
“Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information”.
The UK introduced the amendments on 25 May 2011 through The Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011. The relevant section is below:
6. (1) Subject to paragraph (4), a person shall not store or gain information, or to gain access to information stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user unless the requirements of paragraph (2) are met.
(2) The requirements are that the subscriber or user of that terminal equipment -
(a) is provided with clear and comprehensive information about the purposes of the storage of, or access to, that information; and
(b) has given his or her consent.
(3) Where an electronic communications network is used by the same person to store or access information in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user on more than one occasion, it is sufficient for the purposes of this regulation that the requirements of paragraph (2) are met in respect of the initial use.
(3A) For the purposes of paragraph (2), consent may be signified by a subscriber who amends or sets controls on the internet browser which the subscriber uses or by using another application or programme to signify consent.”
In summary, to comply with the law, we need to give clear information about what the cookies are used for, why, and obtain consent from you, the user. These are the objectives this Policy is set out to achieve.
4.Types of cookies and purpose
Cookies can be categorised in many ways, one is with regards to their longevity, i.e. for how long they are stored in your browser. According to this classification, cookies can either be:
- Session cookies: temporary cookies that identify and track users within our website. These are automatically deleted by your browser when you close your browser or end the session; and
- Persistent cookies: cookies which enable our website to ‘remember’ who you are and your preferences within our website. These cookies are stored in your browser (the specific location depends on the browser and version) for a period of time.
We assess the cookies present in our website periodically, to ensure they are aligned with the requirements of current legislation. For instance, we remove persistent cookies set to hold data for an excessive period of time, which do not meet the principle of storage limitation, as per Article 5.1.e of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
What the cookies do
Reason to have the cookies in our website
Enhance our website’s functionality
Cookies allow us to enhance the functionality of our website so that we can personalise your experience and allow you to use many of the useful features of our website. These cookies are strictly necessary for the proper functioning of the website. For example, we use cookies so we can remember your preferences and the contents of your shopping basket when you return to our website.
Enhance our website’s performance
This type of cookies helps us understand how our website are being used, mainly for analytical purposes, so that we can work on providing an improved user experience. Cookies used for this purpose do not collect information that identifies a user, but the data is aggregated and made anonymous. For example, data on error messages displayed to users will be collected and the developer team will assess whether the problem is prevalent and solve it.
Web beacons and parameter tracking
These cookies and similar software known as web beacons are used to count the number of users visiting our website, or the number of actions made by the users.
Protocol (IP) address and traffic data
A set of data such as IP addresses, access rates, and page views are recorded in our servers.These data do not allow to identify any individual, i.e. no personal data is collected.
5. Changes to our Cookie Policy
We may change this Cookie Policy at any time and from time to time without notice to you, including by publishing a new version on our website. When we will make any change, we will notify you on our website of such change. You can check the top of the document to see the latest version in force. Any change will be prospective only, and we will not make any changes that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so.
6. How to disable cookies?
As cookies are stored in the web browser used to access the website, users need to change the settings pertaining that browser in particular. Below are some of most popular browsers and corresponding links to the vendors’ guidance on disabling cookies:
Internet Explorer:
https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies
https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer
Firefox:
https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/how-do-i-turn-do-not-track-feature
Chrome:
https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en-GB
Safari:
https://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_GB
Opera:
https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/
In addition, Google Analytics gives you the option to install an opt-out browser add-on for Internet Explorer 11, Firefox, Chrome, Safari, and Opera: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
7. Rejecting cookies
Please note that disabling or rejecting the use of cookies on our website may result in some pages becoming inaccessible or not functioning properly.
8. Further information
Several websites explain how cookies work, offering more detail, such as www.aboutcookies.org, and www.allaboutcookies.org. We have no affiliation with these websites.
9. Contacting us
If you have any questions about our Cookie Policy or about how we process your personal data, including any complaints, please contact us by e-mail to compliance@rchmail.com.
Postal Address:
© 2020 Red Carnation Hotels. All Rights Reserved.
